The cure for the common man.
Hitch is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Andy Tennant.
Dating coach Alex 'Hitch' Hitchens mentors a bumbling client, Albert,
who hopes to win the heart of the glamorous Allegra Cole.
While Albert makes progress, Hitch faces his own romantic setbacks when proven techniques fail to
work on Sara Melas, a tabloid reporter digging for dirt on Allegra Cole's love life.
When Sara discovers Hitch's connection to Albert – now Allegra's
boyfriend – it threatens to destroy both relationships.
Hitch, played by Will Smith.
Sara, played by Eva Mendes.
Albert, played by Kevin James.
Allegra, played by Amber Valletta.
Casey, played by Julie Ann Emery.
Max, played by Adam Arkin.
Hitch is a 2005 American romantic comedy film directed by Andy Tennant and starring Will
Smith in the title role, along with Eva Mendes, Kevin James, and Amber Valletta.
The film, which was written by Kevin Bisch, features Smith as a professional
matchmaker who makes a living teaching men how to woo women.
Unfortunately, while helping his latest client woo the woman of his dreams, he finds out
that his game does not work on the gossip columnist with whom he is smitten.
Columbia Pictures released Hitch on February 11, 2005.
The film received positive reviews from critics and was a box office hit, grossing
$371.6 million worldwide, becoming the tenth highest-grossing film of 2005.
The film explores themes of romcom, speed date, dating, romantic.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.